National Railroad Adjustment Board Case Files 5837
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 1606-1729 (Box 23)
  - Docket No. 272. Award No. 273. Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal., 1943-1945 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Docket No. 289. Award No. 275. RA Bosworth., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Docket No. 287. Award No. 276.Southern Railway. Withdrawn., 1945-1947 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Docket No. 287. Award NO. 276. Southern Railway. Assistant Yardmasters., 1943-1947 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Docket No. 290. Award No. 277. West End Harrisburg Station., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Docket No. 277. Award No. 281. HV Gallagher., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Docket No. 278. Award No. 282. Cambridge, Ohio., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Docket No. 279. Award No. 283. LS Musser. HW Snyder., 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Santa Fe. Letters Addressed to Yardmasters., 1941-1945 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Docket No. 281. Award No. 285. FW Kaneaster, et al., 1946 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Docket No. 282. Award No. 286. RH Copple., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Docket No. 284. Award No. 287. Corwith Yard., 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Docket No. 283. Award No. 288. West Dallas, Texas., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Docket No. 296. Award No. 289. Flatbush Avenue, Brooklyn., 1943-1945 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Docket No. 301. Award No. 290. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Case. Emil H. Wiese., 1945 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Docket No. 304. Award No. 291. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. Joseph M Wick., 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Docket No. 299. Award No. 292. Orrville, Ohio., 1944-1946 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Peach Creek, West Virginia. Chesapeake and Ohio Railway. Withdrawn., 1942-1945 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Docket No. 303. Award No. 293. JM Fitzpatrick., 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Docket No. 306. Award No. 294. Pennsylvania Railroad. JC Marsh., 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Docket No. 291. Award No. 295. Market Street Yard., 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Docket No. 297. Award No. 296. TRRA Case. ED Cox., 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Docket No. 298. Award No. 297. WJ Krampf., 1944-1946 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Docket No. 302. Award No. 298. Southern Pacific, Pacific Lines. AM Cunningham Demotion., 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 1741-1849 (Box 24)
  - Award No. 1984. Docket No. 1952. RYA vs. Union Pacific Railroad. RG Heusen., 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 1995. Docket No. 1963. RYA vs. Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation., 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 1999. Docket No. 1986. RYA vs. St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Co., 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 2003. Docket No. 2032. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe., 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 2004. Docket No. 1971. RYA vs. Union Pacific. WK Harr., 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 2007. Docket No. 1988. RYA vs. Union Railroad. PO Miles., 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 2009. Docket No. 1991. RYA vs. Grand Trunk Western Railroad. WH Skinner., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 2019. Docket No. 2009. RYA vs. Washington Terminal Co.BW Boston., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 2020. Docket No. 2010. RYA vs. New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad. LP Lineham., 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 2021. Docket No. 1982. Louisville and Nashville., 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 2022. Docket No. 1990. RYA vs. Port Terminal., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 2032. Docket No. 1983. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe., 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 2033. Docket No. 1997. Cambridge, Ohio. LH362., 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 2034. Docket No. 2006. Pennsylvania Railroad., 1966 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 2034. Docket No. 2006. MT Howell. Akron, Lake Region. Pennsylvania Railroad., 1964-1966 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 2035. Docket No. 2011. RYA vs. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad. EV DeGolier., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 2037. Docket No. 2013. Chicago and North Western. Raymond J Morris., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 2037. Docket No. 2013. RYA vs. Chicago and North Western. RJ Morris., 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 2041. Docket No. 2059. RYA vs. Erie and Lackawanna Railroad Co. Binghamton, NY., 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 2047. Docket No. 2069. Southern Railway. CA Calhoun, Jr. Time Lost., 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 2048. Docket No. 2073. Missouri-Pacific Railroad Co. Monroe, Louisiana., 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 2049. Docket No. 2080. Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis. RW Gunter., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 2057. Docket No. 2023. RYA vs. Erie and Lackawanna Railroad. MJ Smith, Jr., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 1850-1980 (Box 25)
  - Award No. 2058. Docket No. 2026. RYA vs. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific. EF Gasperini., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - RYA Milwaukee Local Lodge No. 92. Reinstatement of EF Gasperini., 1964 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 2069. Docket No. 2110. The Washington Terminal Co. Yardmaster HC Adkins., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 2072. Docket No. 2025. RYA vs. Grand Trunk Western. JW Vaughan., 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 2083. Docket No. 2055. Grand Trunk Western Railroad. WN Roddy., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 2092. Docket No. 2136. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway.TJ McGurk and RB Sullivan., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 2093. Docket No. 2139. Western Maryland Railway Co. Day's Pay., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 2094. Docket No. 2140. Northern Pacific Railway Co. JH Maskie., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 2096. Docket No. 2058. Lehigh Valley Railroad. AJ Thomas., 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 2097. Docket No. 2064. Chesapeake Region. Pennsylvania Railroad. ER Pollack., 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 2098. Docket No. 2065. Missouri-Pacific Railroad Co. HH Love et al. Illinois Yard., 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 2099. Docket No. 2066. Norfolk and Western Railway. GW Schmieding., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 2103. Docket No. 2076. Missouri-Pacific Personal Record of AV Dixon., 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 2104. Docket No. 2077. The Detroit and Toledo Shore Line Railroad Co., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 2115. Docket No. 2083. Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis Yard. TL McGarvy., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 2116. Docket No. 2041. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. Bullard and Daws., 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 2117. Docket No. 2042. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway., 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 2118. Docket No. 2043. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway System., 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 2119. Docket No. 2072. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway System., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 2120. Docket No. 2126. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway System. JE Mount, TJ Hylek., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 2121. Docket No. 2155. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. WE Lee, Jr. Sick Pay., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 2122. Docket No. 2079. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. EG Hardin., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 2128. Docket No. 2106. The Washington Terminal Co. HC Adkins., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 2136. Docket No. 2142. Norfolk and Western. CF Davison., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 2137. Docket No. 2157. Pennsylvania Railroad. GB Potash., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 2139. Docket No. 2163. Grand Trunk Western. HE Doll., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 2140. Docket No. 2169. Grand Trunk Western. HE Doll., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 2141. Docket No. 2097. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. CL Kelshaw and JW Walton, Jr., 1957-1966 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Award No. 2142. Docket No. 2109. Lehigh Valley., 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 1984-2142 (Box 26)
  - Award No. 1090. Docket No. 1086. Pittsburgh Lake Erie. MJ Smith., 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 1091. Docket No. 1087. Pittsburgh Lake Erie. JV Flaherty., 1954-1956 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 1163. Docket No. 1150. Chicago and North Western. WI Snyder. Nelson, Illinois., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 1162. Docket No. 1149. Chicago and North Western. McElderry., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 1098. Docket No. 1094. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 1099. Docket No. 1095. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. NF Logsdon., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 1100. Docket No. 1096. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific. HH Oerke., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 1104. Docket No. 1114. Chicago and North Western. AF Peterson Claim., 1954-1956 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 1105. Docket No. 1041. Grand Trunk Western. W. Swenson., 1953-1956 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 1108. Docket No. 1024. Pennsylvania Railroad. CW Allen Disqualification., 1954-1956 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 1110. Docket No. 1063. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. HC Bowen., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 115. Docket No. 1121. Baltimore and Ohio. JC Renforth., 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 1116. Docket No. 1122. Baltimore and Ohio. WH Bell., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 1117. Docket No. 1119. Baltimore and Ohio. RT Joyce., 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 1118. Docket No. 1120. Baltimore and Ohio. RT Joyce., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 1119. Docket No. 1123. Baltimore and Ohio. PB Daniels., 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 1126. Docket No. 1115. Chicago Great Western. JP Fletcher., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 1127. Docket No. 1116. Chicago Great Western. JP Fletcher., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 1140. Docket No. 1132. Baltimore and Ohio. FF Maloney., 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 1143. Docket No. 1128. Chicago and North Western. SJ Zatone., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 1150. Docket No. 1186. Chicago and North Western. FM Manrose., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 1151. Docket No. 1138. Chicago and North Western. JT Holleran., 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 1089. Docket No. 1085. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie. JV Flaherty., 1954-1956 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 1173. Docket No. 1173. TRRA. EE Foresee., 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 1172. Docket No. 1157. New York Central. DM Wilson Disqualification., 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 1158. Docket No. 1145. Chicago and North Western. WV Arter., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 1156. Docket No. 1143. Chicago and North Western. Weber Yard Case., 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 1155. Docket No. 1142. Chicago and North Western. TE Hayes., 1952-1957 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 2147-2257 (Box 27)
  - Award No. 3041. Docket No. 2991. Burlington Northern. FD Eastman., 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 3042. Docket No. 2992. Burlington Northern Railroad Yard. JF Turya., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 3043. Docket No. 2993. Burlington Railroad. Northern Railroad. BB Ball., 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 3044. Docket No. 3027. Union Pacific Railroad Co. HL Price., 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 3046. Docket No. 3043. Detroit Terminal Railroad Co. R. Laesser., 1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 3047. Docket No. 3068. The Texas and Pacific Railway Co. JC Collins., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 3048. Docket No. 3069. The Texas and Pacific Railway Co. Yard. JC Collins., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 3049. Docket No. 3070. The Texas and Pacific Railway Co. S Smith et al., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 3050. Docket No. 3074. Erie Lackawanna Railway Co. TP Pete., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 3053. Docket No. 3032. Penn Central Transport Co. System Docket 429. RYA 6-72., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    Pittsburgh Territory, Cleveland Case.
  - Award No. 3054. Docket No. 3034. Lehigh and New England Railway Co. John R Williams., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 3055. Docket No. 3035. Penn Central Transport Co. System Docket 428. RYA 3-72., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 3056. Docket No. 3050. Lackawanna and New England Railway Co. Morris O Williams., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 3057. Docket No. 3058. Penn Central Yard. Thomas Lanutti. System Docket No. 432. Case 41-71., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Philadelphia Territory, Philadelphia Case.
  - Award No. 3059. Docket No. 3081. Union Pacific Railroad Co. JL Durham., 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 3060. Docket No. 3082. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. RK Russell., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 3061. Docket No. 3088. Seaboard Coast Line Railroad Co. Belk, Honeycutt, et al., 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 3062. Docket No. 3031. Louisiana Junction Railway Co. HE Birkholm., 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 3063. Docket No. 3033. Lackawanna and New England Railway Co. Morris O Williams and Ralph M Stampone., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 3064. Docket No. 3036. Central Railroad Co. of New Jersey. Wallinger., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 3067. Docket No. 3048. Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis. FM Pugh., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 3069. Docket No. 3095. Boston and Maine Corporation Yard. HW Martel., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 3070. Docket No. 3106. Penn Central. Burns. Harbor, Indiana., 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 3071. Docket No. 3118. Penn Central. AJ DePalma. System Docket 454. Case No. 435., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    Northern Region, Michigan Division.
  - Award No. 3075. Docket No. 3063. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. RL Barker., 1974 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 3076. Docket No. 3080. Penn Central. JC Snyder. System Docket 438. Case 21-72-98., 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    North Eastern Territory, Buffalo Case.
  - Award No. 3078. Docket No. 3124. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. GW Reed., 1974 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 2258-2393 (Box 28)
  - Award No. 3003. Docket No. 2995. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. Chevrolet Yardmasters., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 3004. Docket No. 2996. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. FR Hoskin., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 3005. Docket No. 2997. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. Doll, Fisher et al., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 3007. Docket No. 2867. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific. LA Pacific., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 3008. Docket No. 2868. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific. GH Correll., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 3009. Docket No. 2880. Union Pacific Railroad. HL Rowberry., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Award No. Renewal 3009-A. Docket No. Renewal 2880., 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 3010. Docket No. 2920. Penn Central. W Winchester., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 3013. Docket No. 2999. Erie Lackawanna. AP Dressage., 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 3015. Docket No. 3001. Boston and Maine. RF Bruso., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 3016. Docket No. 3004. Los Angeles Junction. HW Storms., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 3017. Docket No. 3005. Chesapeake and Ohio. LW Showalter., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 3018. Docket No. 300 Chicago and North Western Transportation Co. RL Mallas., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 3019. Docket No. 3039. Western Maryland Railway Co. Case No. 92. FE Kozel., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 3020. Docket No. 3040. Lackawanna and New England Railway Co. JR Williams., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 3021. Docket No. 3041. Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis. CF Weinert., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 3022. Docket No. 3042. Boston and Maine Corporation. TF Sullivan, Jr., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 3023. Docket No. 3002. Union Pacific Railroad., 1971-1974 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 3024. Docket No. 3008. Norfolk and Western. AL Bird., 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 3025. Docket No. 3013. Central of New Jersey. Raymond J Havens., 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 3026. Docket No. 3014. Central Railroad Co. of New Jersey. Howard Maybin., 1974 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 3027. Docket No. 3015. Central Railroad of New Jersey. Joseph S Magliano., 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 3032. Docket No. 3049. Burlington Northern., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 3034. Docket No. 3011. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. PC Mertens., 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 3035. Docket No. 3012. Norfolk and Western. John M Donges., 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 3036. Docket No. 3021. Norfolk and Western. Frank A Chambers., 1974 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 3037. Docket No. 3022. Norfolk and Western. James R David., 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 3038. Docket No. 3023. Norfolk and Western Railway Co. New River Division. CB Franklin., 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Award No. 3039. Docket No. 3025. Norfolk and Western Railway Co. RE Elliott., 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Award No. 3040. Docket No. 3053. Boston and Maine Corporation. Debtor Martel et al., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 2394-2488 (Box 29)
  - Award No. 2897. Docket No. 2767. Southern Railway. JW Caldwell., 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 2898. Docket No. 2768. Southern Railway. BF Pelt., 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 2899. Docket No. 2769. Southern Railway. WW Gibson., 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 2900. Docket No. 2770. Southern Railway. HL Dorton., 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 2901. Docket No. 2771. Southern Railway. GW Autry., 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 2902. Docket No. 2772. Southern Railway. JA Cameron., 1973 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 2903. Docket No. 2830. Penn Central System Docket 386. Case 46-71. JJ Williams., 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 2905. Docket No. 2973. BF Pelt. Southern Railway System., 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 2907. Docket No. 2975. Texas and Pacific. JG Collins., 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 2908. Docket No. 2976. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. RL Nedrow., 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 2909. Docket No. 2977. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. JR Oldland et al., 1973 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 2910. Docket No. 2891. Western Maryland Railway Co. HW Harp, Jr., 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 2911. Docket No. 2892. Western Maryland Railway Co. JM Bone-Brake, Jr., 1973 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Western Maryland Railway Co. HL Smith., 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 2913. Docket No. 2894. Western Maryland Railway Co. HA Morris., 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 2914. Docket No. 2895. Western Maryland Railway Co. GB Hallowell., 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 2489-2602 (Box 30)
  - Award No. 2889. Docket No. 2759. Southern Railway System. JL Joly., 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 2890. Docket No. 2760. Southern Railway. DR Wardlow., 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 2891. Docket No. 2761. Southern Railway. KJ Delk., 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 2892. Docket No. 2762. Southern Railway. CN Turner., 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 2893. Docket No. 2763. Southern Railway. JL Roy., 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 2894. Docket No. 2764. Southern Railway. CT Bridges., 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 2895. Docket No. 2765. Southern Railway System. JC Stover., 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 2896. Docket No. 2766. Southern Railway. HM Wilson., 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 2606-2683 (Box 31)
  - RYA and the Pacific Electric Yardmasters. Correspondence., 1963 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Electric Railway Co. Representation., 1937-1963 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Penn Central Representation. Invocation., 1968 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    March 1 1968.
  - Penn Central Representation. Invocation. March 1 1968. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Reading Co. Representation., 1956-1965 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Pittsburgh and Ohio Valley Representation., 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - St. Louis Southwestern. Cotton belt Representation., 1955-1964 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Philadelphia, Bethlehem and New England. Representation., 1925-1963 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - New York and Penn Central Yardmasters, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac. Representation., 1924-1960 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Co. Bound Documents., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - New York Central Railroad Documents, 1942-1946 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - RYA Representation Authorization Cards, 1942-1944 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - New York Central and Miscellaneous Documents, 1946-1954 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Various Union Documents., 1949 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - SUNA and RYA Documents., 1947-1949 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - New York, Susquehanna and Western. Representation., 1955 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - South Buffalo. Representation., 1952 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Texas and New Orleans. Representation., 1943-1953 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Union Railroad Company. Representation., 1958 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - National Mediation Board. Washington Terminal Company., 1963 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Seaboard Air Line. Representation., 1953 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Washington Terminal Representation. Initiated by RYA. Case R-3610., 1963 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - RYA and AFL-CIO. Union Shop Agreement., 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - RYA Accordance with AFL-CIO Constitution., 1963 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - RYA and AFL-CIO. Dispute., 1963 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - List of Yardmasters and Questionnaires., 1954-1963 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Washington. Terminal., 1960 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Western Maryland. Representation. File No. C-3074., 1961 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Washington Terminal Representation. Case No. R-3443., 1961 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Washington Terminal Co. and Western Pacific., 1945-1953 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- RYA Cases disposed of by N.R.A.B. Fourth Division Awards 2684-2803 (Box 32)
  - Award No. 2858. Docket No. 2804. Baltimore and Ohio. RT Augostine., 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 2859. Docket No. 2805. Baltimore and Ohio. LJ Boyer., 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 2860. Docket No. 2816. Penn Central. Pittsburgh Territory. Docket 359. Mingo Junction. TR Albaugh., 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 2862. Docket No. 2837. Union Belt of Detroit. MR McClure., 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 2870. Docket No. 2875. Missouri Pacific. RL McCarty, Brownsville Texas., 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 2871. Docket No. 2876. Missouri Pacific. RH Ketchum, Harlington Texas., 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 2873. Docket No. 2884. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. RM King., 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 2874. Docket No. 2889. Central of New Jersey. L Irving., 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 2875. Docket No. 2854. Southern Railway System. JL Joly, Jr., 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 9)